A Guide to the Records of the Communications Office of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1989-1994 (bulk 1990-1993).
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Publications featuring Governor Wilder, 1990-1993 (Acc. 35539)., Extent: 1.75 cubic feet (5 boxes). (Box 50-54)
  Publications featuring Gov. Wilder, 1990-1993, are housed in 5 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by name of the publication. Each publication includes an article about or interview with Gov. Wilder. Includes the entire original publication and may also include a photocopy of the individual article.
  - Albemalre, 1993 Aug-Sept. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Albemarle, 1993 Oct-Nov. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Gazette (College of William and Mary), 1993 Mar. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - American Libraries, 1993 Oct. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - The Atlantic, 1993 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - The Backstretch, 1993 June/July. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - The Banner, 1993. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education, 1990 Sept. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - The Blood Horse, 1993 Apr 24. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Campaigns and Elections - The Magazine of Political Professionals, 1993 Apr/May. (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Campaigns and Elections - The Magazine of Political Professionals, 1993 Dec / 1994 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Cato Policy Reports, 1992 July/Aug. (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - CitiLimits, 1992 Oct. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - City and State, 1993 May 10-23. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - City and State, 1993 June 21-July 4. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Cortland Forum, 1993 Mar. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - The Crisis, 1993 Mar. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Ebony, 1991 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Ebony, 1993 June. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - The Economic Review, 1993-1994: A Guide to Japanese-American Economic and Cultural Relations in the Southeast United States (v. VIII), 1993. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - The Economist, 1993 Mar 13-19. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - The Economist, 1993 Apr 3-9. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Export Virginia, 1992 Oct. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Financial World (FW), 1993 May 11-12. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Financial World (FW), 1993 June 8. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Focus (For and about the people of AT and T), 1993 Mar/Apr. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Forbes, 1992 Dec 7. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Fortune, 1993 July 26. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Governing (The Magazine of States and Localities), 1993 Mar. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Jet, 1992 June 8. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Jet, 1992 Oct 19. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Jet, 1993 Feb 15. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Jet, 1993 Mar 22. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Jet, 1993 Apr 5. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Jet, 1993 May 17. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Jet, 1993 June 28. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Jet, 1993 Aug 2. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Jet, 1993 Nov 22. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Jet, 1993 Dec 6. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Jet, 1993 Dec 13. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - JULUKA (A Newsletter for Southern Africans in North America), 1992 Oct/Nov. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - KUSEC Newsletter (Korea - U.S. Economic Council), 1993 Oct 30. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Money, 1993 Oct. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - NBA Magazine (National Bar Association), 1990 July. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - National Black Review, 1990 June/July. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - The New Republic, 1990 Aug 30. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Newsweek, 1991 May 6. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Newsweek (Special Election Issue), 1992 Nov/Dec. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Newseek, 1993 Oct 25. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - New York, 1991 Apr 15. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - New York Times Magazine, 1992 Jan 12. (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - New York Times Magazine, 1992 Mar 8. (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - The New Yorker, 1993 Mar 22. (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Profiles International, 1992 Nov/Dec. (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Playboy, 1991 Sept. (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Reader's Digest, 1991 July. (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Reader's Digest, 1993 Sept. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Regardie's, 1990 July/. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Regardie's, 1990 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Regardie's, 1990 Dec / 1992 Jan. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Regardie's, 1992 Aug/Sept. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - The Southern Christian Leadership Conference National Magazine, 1992 Aug-Oct. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Southern Growth, 1993 Fall. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Southern Political Report, 1993 Mar 16. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Southern Political Report, 1993 July 6. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Spy, 1991 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Time, 1992 Aug 24. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Time, 1993 Mar 29. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1991 May 13. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1993 Mar 29. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1993 Oct 4. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Business, 1991 Feb. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Business, 1992 Jan. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Business, 1992 July. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Business, 1992 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Business, 1992 Dec. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 Feb. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 Apr. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 June. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 July. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Business, 1993 Sept. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Mining Journal, 1993. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Southwest, 1991. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Town and City, 1993 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Washingtonian, 1993 Dec. (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Series VIII. Newspaper Clippings by Subject, 1989-1991 (Acc. 35581)., Extent: 3.5 cubic feet (10 boxes). (Box 55-64)
  New Clippings by Subject, 1989-1991, are housed in 10 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by subject. This series includes photocopies of news articles from both state and national newspapers. The bulk of these clippings were gathered and organized between January-May of 1990, when the topical collection and arrangment of news clippings seems to have abandoned. Also includes bound sets of news clipping relating to the 1989 gubernatorial election (incomplete - gaps in coverage) and 1991 news articles about Presidential candidates. See also Series IX. News summaries, for news articles in chronological order, 1990 June-1994 Jan.
  - Abortion, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Administration, Secretary of, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Air and Space Museum (Smithsonian), 1990. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, Hunter B., 1990. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Appointments, 1990-1991. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Beyer, Don, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Bond Pledge, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Budget - Federal, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Budget - Virginia, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Bush, George, 1990. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial, 1989 Mar-May. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial, 1989 June-July. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial, 1989 Aug. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial, 1989 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial (Part II - Part I was not transferred and neither were clippings from Nov), 1989 Oct. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial (Part I), 1989 Dec. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, Gubernatorial (Part II), 1989 Dec. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Campaign contributions, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Campaigns, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Capital punishment, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Census, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Chesapeake Bay, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia, 1990. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Congress, U.S., 1990. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Delegation, Virginia, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Courts, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - CSX - RFP, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Defense - National, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Party - National, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Party - Virginia, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Dinkins, David, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Disparity, Educational, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Divestment, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Drugs, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Drugs, Non-prescription, 1990. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Dulles (United Airlines), 1990. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Mar. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990 Apr-May. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1990 Mar. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1990 Apr. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Education, Secretary of, 1990 May. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Employment, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Energy, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - European Trade Mission, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Far East Trade Mission, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Film Festival, 1991. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Finance, Secretary of, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, 1990 Jan. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, 1990 Feb. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, 1990 Mar. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly, 1990 Apr. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Goldman, Paul, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - GOP, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Governors, 1990. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - GreekFest, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Gun Control, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Secretary of, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Housing, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Inaugural Funds, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Kim-Stan and other Landfills, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Kluges, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Local government, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Mansion, Executive, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - National political figures, 1990. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1990 Mar. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1990 Apr. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1990 May. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Northern Virginia, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Pensions, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Persian Gulf Crisis, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Pittston Coal, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Ports, 1990. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Presidential Candidates - Gov. Jerry Brown, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Candidates - Gov. Bill Clinton, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Candidates - Gov. Mario Cuomo, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Candidates - Sen. Tom Harkin, 1991. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Candidates - Sen. Bob Kerrey, 1991. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Candidates - Sen. Paul Tsongas, 1991. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Public Safety, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Public Safety, Secretary of, 1990 Mar-Apr. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Public Safety, Secretary of, 1990 May. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Recycling, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Redistricting, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Robb, Chuck, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Rural Economic Development, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Savings and Loans, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Shropshire, Jay, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Smithfield Foods, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Smoking, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Terry, Mary Sue, 1990. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Transportation, Secretary of, 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Transportation Secretary of, 1990 Mar-Apr. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, Secretary of, 1990 May. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute (VMI), 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute (VMI), 1990 Mar-May. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Warner, John, 1990. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Wilder, Gov. L. Douglas, 1990 Jan-Feb. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Wilder, Gov. L. Douglas, 1990 Mar-May. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Wilder, Gov. L. Douglas (National), 1990. (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Series IX. News Summaries, 1990 June-1994 Jan (Acc. 35539)., Extent: 22 cubic feet (22 boxes). (Box 3-24)
  News Summaries, 1990-1994, are housed in 22 boxes and are arranged chronologically. These news summaries consist of photocopies of news articles of interest that were distributed to the Governor and his staff on a nearly daily basis.
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 June 9-10. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 11. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition, Part I), 1990 June 11. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition, Part II), 1990 June 11. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 12. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 13. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 14. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 18. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 19. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 20. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 21. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 22. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 25. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 June 25. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries (Part I), 1990 June 26. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries (Part II), 1990 June 26. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries (Part I), 1990 June 27. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries (Part II), 1990 June 27. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 28. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1990 June 29. (Box 3a, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 July 2. (Box 3a, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 2. (Box 3a, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 3. (Box 3a, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 5. (Box 3a, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 6. (Box 3a, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 July 9. (Box 3a, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 12. (Box 3a, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 16. (Box 3a, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 July 16. (Box 3a, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 17. (Box 3a, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 19. (Box 3a, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 20. (Box 3a, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 23. (Box 3a, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries (Weekend Edition), 1990 July 23. (Box 3a, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 24. (Box 3a, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 25. (Box 3b, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 26. (Box 3b, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 27. (Box 3b, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 July 31. (Box 3b, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 1. (Box 3b, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 2. (Box 3b, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 2. (Box 3b, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 3. (Box 3b, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 6. (Box 3b, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 7. (Box 3b, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 8. (Box 3b, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 9. (Box 3b, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 10. (Box 3b, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 13. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 14. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 15. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 16. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 17. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 19. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 20. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 21. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 22. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 23. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 24. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 27. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 28. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 29. (Box 4a, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 30. (Box 4a, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Aug 31. (Box 4a, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 3. (Box 4a, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 4. (Box 4a, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 5. (Box 4a, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 6. (Box 4a, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 7. (Box 4a, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 10. (Box 4a, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 11. (Box 4a, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 12. (Box 4a, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 13. (Box 4a, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 17. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 18. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 19. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 20. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 21. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 24. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 25. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 26. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 27. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Sept 28. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 2. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 3. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 4. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 5. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 9. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 10. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 11. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 12. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 15. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 16. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 17. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 18. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 19. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 22. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 23. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 24. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 25. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 26. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 29. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 30. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Oct 31. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 1. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 2. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 5. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 6. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 7. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 8. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 9. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 12. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 14. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 15. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 16. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 19. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 20. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 21. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 27. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 28. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 29. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Nov 30. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 3. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 4. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 5. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 6. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 10. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 11. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 12. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 13. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 14. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 17. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 18. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 19. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 20. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1990 Dec 21. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 2. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 3. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 4. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 7. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 8. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 9. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 10. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 11. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 14. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 15. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 16. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 17. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 18. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 21. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 22. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 23. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 24. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 25. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 28. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 29. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 30. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Jan 31. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 1. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 4. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 5. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 6. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 7. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 8. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 11. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 12. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 13. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 14. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 15. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 18. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 19. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 20. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 21. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 22. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 25. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 26. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 27. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Feb 28. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 1. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 4. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 5. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 6. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 7. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 8. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 11. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 12. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 13. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 14. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 15. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 18. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 19. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 20. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 21. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 22. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 25. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 26. (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 27. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 28. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Mar 29. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 1. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 2. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 3. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 4. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 5. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 8. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 9. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 10. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 11. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 12. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 15. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 16. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 17. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 18. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 19. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 22. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 23. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 24. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - News Summaries, 1991 Apr 25. (Box 8, Folder 19)